Hey Nick, welcome back to India, I
guess.
>> Thank you.
>> So, you're you play at IU, national
champion IU now, by the way. It's crazy
crazy to say, I'm sure. Um, and then you
were kind of a cult killer when you were
with the Titans. So, how did it work out
that you found yourself back here in
Indiana?
>> Yeah. Uh, it's funny. My my buddy would
always say that back in Tennessee. Um,
and that's how I told him I broke the
news. I was like, I'm switching sides.
Uh, but I'm excited to. Um, I mean it's
a great organization. It's a team I've
always, you know, been a fan of. Uh,
just being at IU and growing up, you
know, watching Reggie Wayne, Marvin
Harrison, like you're always I've kind
of always been a fan of the team. Um,
but then just this the season they had
last year, I can see what they're
building. I've always seen it as a team
that has a great culture um, and
something I want to be a part of. So, it
just it worked out. It was definitely,
you know, going into free agency this
year. I told my agent like, "Look, if
Indie is an option, I' I'd love to be
there."
>> James
>> Nick, was part of that reason you wanted
to explore the possibility of coming to
Indianapolis because of Daniel Jones?
>> Uh, yeah. I mean, that's part of it. you
know, having an established quarterback
and a guy that, you know, the level he
was playing at, you could see, um, he's
just a professional all around and was
just talking with, uh, Coach Stiken and
just, you know, the way he works, his
his work ethic, his mentality. Um, that
definitely helps being a part of an
established, you know, quarterback room
where you have, you know, a guy. If you
have a quarterback, you got a chance to
win games.
>> And then one followup, um, kind of a
down year, I guess, statistically for
yourself last year. How would you
explain the year in Miami and also what
you have clearly left in the tank? I'm
not saying you're going to retire
anytime soon, but just, you know,
playing the game.
>> Yeah. Um, yeah. I mean, it was just
unfortunate. You know, I can't put my
finger on it. You know, if it was just
wasn't the right fit or, you know, lack
of chemistry, whatever it might be. Um,
but I'm excited for this new
opportunity. Um, I feel like that's also
kind of getting me a little bit more
motivated. just the excitement of being
here, being, you know, it's kind of a
hometown team. Got a bunch of family. My
wife grew up in Brownsburg right down
the road. You know, I'd drive by the
facility every time I'd come visit her
family in the offseason and even when I
was in Tennessee. So, a lot to play for.
Just adding a new another son to the
mix. So, yeah, I'm excited to be here.
>> Lara,
>> Nick, welcome to Indie. You mentioned
you had a chance to chat with coach
Dikken and you're you've said you grew
up a fan of Reggie. Have you had a
chance to meet with your new wide
receivers, coach? Immediate impressions
and where you can benefit most working
with him.
>> Haven't met with him yet. Um but
definitely looking forward to it. Uh you
know, I got a lot of respect for him as
a player. Uh he's one of the greatest.
So yeah, looking forward to that that
meeting and and just finding a way I can
can fill in and you know, carve a roll
out. You know, I feel like every time
every year I've been in the league, I'm
never going into it thinking I'm owed
anything and definitely not coming in
this year after the year I just had. So,
I have I have some work to do. I got to,
you know, earn my spot and earn my keep
um and just find a way that I can help
this team win.
>> We'll go with Stephen and then Joel will
be our last question.
>> Hey, Nick. um you you know when you've
you've played in a couple different
places, different different offenses,
and I'm wondering is does that provide
you maybe some advantage to coming into
a situation where you kind of have to be
ready for anything in terms of what your
role might be? We don't know, but there
are a couple established guys in that
room. You kind of just, you know, got to
be ready to go if if called upon. Um how
does that your history maybe help you?
Yeah, I mean I feel like that's
something I try to hang my hat on and
just being a constant learner of the
game. Uh even from back in college, uh
you know, I had several different
offensive coordinators and bunch
throughout my career in the league so
far. So I try to pick up on offensive
offenses fast, pick up on the playbook.
Um and that's when I feel like I play my
best, when I have a full grasp and
understanding on, you know, the play
calling and what everybody's got.
And Joel, last question.
>> One of your calling cards in Tennessee
was that you you're pretty good at
getting deep. Um making a big play down
the field. What do you think is it leads
to that for you skill set wise?
>> I mean, just being a bigger receiver. Uh
you know, you're big and you're fast.
You know, it just gives you a better
opportunity down the field. Um but
honestly, part of that too is just the I
feel like the cerebral part of the game.
And you know, we'd have a lot of things,
you know, when I was in Tennessee,
whether it was, you know, I mean, the 98
yard touchdown I had a couple years ago.
It was just I knew the look and I was
like, "This ball is coming to me. I'm
not going to slow down." And it's kind
of a a play that you normally kind of
run it just for the love of the game and
I chose not to that time. Um, but then
just, you know, being on top of
defenses, being able to read a defense
and know where the hole is going to be.
>> Did you go to the national championship
game?
>> Oh, yeah. Oh, yeah.
What was that experience like?
>> It was incredible. It was special. I
actually had saw the I told you about my
my in-laws live right down the road. I
brought uh my dad or my father-in-law
and my two brother-in-laws and we all
went to the game. It was a blast.
>> Thanks for your time, Nick. That should
do it. Thank you.